{
    "subject": "resource/Battle_of_the_Espero_Convoy",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Naval_battles_of_World_War_II_involving_Italy",
    "human_readable": "The Battle of the Espero Convoy is about Naval battles of World War II involving Italy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8817387223243713,
            "question": "Which country's navy participated in the Battle of the Espero Convoy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7645322680473328,
            "question": "Where did the Battle of the Espero Convoy occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7304161787033081,
            "question": "What type of military conflict was the Battle of the Espero Convoy involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6851971745491028,
            "question": "What was the main objective of the Battle of the Espero Convoy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6180197596549988,
            "question": "Were there any notable ships involved in the Battle of the Espero Convoy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6134911179542542,
            "question": "When did the Battle of the Espero Convoy take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.594187319278717,
            "question": "What were the consequences of the Battle of the Espero Convoy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5319852232933044,
            "question": "How is the Battle of the Espero Convoy remembered historically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5192365646362305,
            "question": "Who were the key participants on each side of the Battle of the Espero Convoy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4887792766094208,
            "question": "What strategic importance did the Battle of the Espero Convoy hold?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Battle of the Espero Convoy is about Naval battles of World War II involving Italy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_260_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were the key participants on each side of the Battle of the Espero Convoy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_260_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is the Battle of the Espero Convoy remembered historically?",
            "html": "dbpedia_260_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the consequences of the Battle of the Espero Convoy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_260_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_260_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_260_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_260_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_260_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_260_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_260_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_260_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_260_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_260_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_260_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe triple statement is: \"The Battle of the Espero Convoy is about Naval battles of World War II involving Italy.\"\n\nUpon reviewing the provided context information, we can see that all the documents mention the Battle of the Espero Convoy as a naval engagement fought between British-led and Italian forces in the Mediterranean Sea during World War II. The documents also specify that it was the first surface engagement in the Mediterranean Sea in World War II (8 June 1940) and provide details about the battle, including the involvement of various ships and warships.\n\nTherefore, based on this information, we can confirm that the triple statement is correct, and the value for \"output\" should be \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the naval engagements and actions during World War II, including references to the Battle of the Espero Convoy as a significant naval battle involving Italian forces. Therefore, the statement that \"The Battle of the Espero Convoy is about Naval battles of World War II involving Italy\" is supported by the context information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}